♪ You woke up this morning
Got yourself a gun ♪
♪ Your mama always said
You'd be the chosen one ♪
♪ She said
"You're one in a million ♪
♪ And you've got to burn
To shine" ♪
♪ But you were born
Under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ And you woke up this morning
And all that love had gone ♪
♪ Your papa never told you
About right and wrong ♪
♪ But you're looking good
Baby ♪
♪ I believe that
You're a-feelin' fine ♪
♪ No shame about it ♪
♪ Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Sing it now ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You got a blue moon ♪
♪ Got a blue moon
In your eyes ♪
♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ You say you woke up
This morning ♪
♪ The world turned
Upside down ♪
♪ Lordy. brother
Things ain't been the same ♪
♪ Since the blues
Walked in our town ♪
♪ But you're one in a million ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
That shotgun shine ♪
♪ No shame about it
Born under a bad sign ♪
♪ With a blue moon
In your eyes. yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Woke up this morning ♪
♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
- ♪ Got yourself a gun ♪
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
So. you know.
usual girl stuff.
She picks up the dry cleaning.
She does the food shopping.
Oh. and by the way. your
Dr. Melfi has excellent taste.
She only shops
at the fancy-schmancy deli.
you know. the kind
with the Italian name.
but you can't find a fucki"
meatball in the whole joint?
What else?
I don't even know what I'm
supposed to be lookin' for here.
- What's up with this cooze?
- It's none of your
fuckin' business.
You're on a strict
need-to-know. Lieutenant.
And I oughta knock the shit
outta ya for what you did
to her date last month.
What? I figure this girl
is some goomar of yours.
so I scare him a little.
What's the big deal?
- This guy still come around?
- No. He's not her type.
I told you. he's a coward.
He nearly pissed himself.
All right. anything else?
I don't wanna be here all day.
Yesterday...
yesterday. she got off at 9:00
and she went to bed early.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Here. Buy yourself an iron.
You ready?
Decaf. right?
So how was your college trip
with your daughter?
Tell ya. my life.
it's like an episode
of Provoloneysomething.
- What's goin' on?
- My wife.
All we do is fight.
Can you believe it?
She's jealous of you.
Is that something
that you feel.
or has there been some
discussion with Carmela?
She didn't know
you were a girl.
You know. a woman.
Excuse me. a doctor.
Woman doctor.
Why did it take you
so long to tell her?
I didn't tell her.
You spilled the beans
when you called
to change the appointment.
Let me ask you
a different question.
Why a female?
Why a female doctor?
You know. she asked
the same friggin' question.
- And I sometimes wonder myself.
- And?
I'll tell you what I told her.
Cusomano gave me a choice
between two Jewish guys
and a paisan like me.
So I picked the paisan.
What's the one thing
every woman.
your mother. your wife.
your daughter. have in common?
They all break my balls.
No. I know what you mean.
They're all Italian. So what?
So maybe by coming
clean with me.
you're dialoguing
with them.
Let me ask you a question.
Why do you have me
as a patient?
Most legit people I know.
they'd go a hundred miles
out of their way not
to make eye contact with me.
But you... you didn't flinch.
The water's warm.
Come on in.
Hey. Sammy. How are you?
Just in time. I was just
gonna make some coffee.
- Yeah?
- How's Junior?
Sit the fuck down! Down!
That's how Junior is. Sammy.
I'm with Little Jimmy Altieri.
Yeah? You payin'
Jimmy for this game?
- Huh. Sammy?
- No.
Are you payin' someone
for this game?
Huh?
The party's over.
Junior Soprano is the new boss.
and he ain't respectin'
old arrangements.
You're lucky. You stayed slim.
You can buy right off the rack.
I wanted something special.
The boys are having
a little time for me.
You're wearin' the suit
to the dinner. eh?
These guys today.
they want to be buried
in their joggin' outfit.
So how's your...
what's your oldest boy's name?
- Raffaele. Ralphie.
- Yeah.
- Good kid.
- Yeah. He lost his son.
you know.
- What do you mean. lost?
- Dead. Morte.
Uh... just a...
just a fucking kid.
A baby.
Oh. what are
we talkin' about here?
- You lost your grandson?
- What are you gonna do?
These fucking animals.
These... these drug dealers.
That little kid used to run
around here breakin' balls.
Dominic. My namesake.
Did you know about this?
See? What'd I say
about this fucking poison?
These kids shouldn't touch it.
I read the paper every day
about these
poor pricks overdosin'.
He didn't overdose.
He killed himself.
- Fourteen years old.
- Jesus!
Was this at Paterson Falls?
Holy shit!
That was your grandson?
- What?
- The kid. he took one of those
designer drugs. right?
Goes to the falls.
takes a header
right off the fence.
They said the current
whirled so much
that his head was bashin'
on the rocks for days
before he even came up.
And meanwhile.
this piece of shit.
he gets to walk the streets
and sell more of this stuff
to young kids.
Oh. really? What's this
motherless fuck's name?
- Even the coffee's old in here.
- How much complaining
can you do?
Eventually. they find you
with a broken hip.
I want to make a gift
of a maganet. That's the only
way you'll get good coffee.
- A maganet.
- What are you wearing?
You smell like a French putan'.
It's Canoe. Johnny wore Canoe.
- Morning. Livia.
- Oh. good morning.
- Morning.
- Hi.
- New arrival?
- Keep moving. fella.
I'm happy for you. Junior.
I know how long you waited
to be made boss.
Just don't let certain people
take advantage
of your good nature
like they did to Johnny.
What certain people?
Nobody got over on Johnny.
Nobody's gonna get over on me.
- How's your Jewish friend?
- Hesh? What about him?
Who ever heard
of a Jew riding horses?
- He owns a horse farm.
- Ah!
He's Tony's friend.
not mine.
What do you
got against him anyway?
Who. me? Nothing.
Johnny liked him.
and my son thinks every word
that comes out of his mouth
is pure gold.
Are you tellin' me
that since I'm the new boss.
I should tax Hesh?
Boy. Anthony must've really
gotten under your collar.
Admit it.
You're lookin'
to crack his coglioni
for puttin' you in here.
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Yeah. And I'm playin'
shortstop for the Mets.
Oh! All right.
watch the balls!
What is the matter?
Tony's cannoli
doesn't want to stand up?
Tony's cannoli's tired.
But I can make it
happen. baby.
I know.
It's just. maybe...
- So how's your job?
- What?
Since when do you care
about my job?
Can't I be nice?
All right. Forget it.
Mmm.
Okay. you don't want
to talk about your job? Fine.
Here. Blow somebody
who gives a fuck.
I'm not a fucking whore!
Stick your money up your ass!
I don't know what's
wrong with you. but don't
take it out on me.
Hey. there's nothing
wrong with me!
Just wanted to talk.
that's all.
For all the conversation
I get around here.
I might as well be
a fuckin' dildo!
If you were a dildo.
we wouldn't be fighting.
What does that mean?
Huh. you fuckin' refugee?
What does that mean? Ah!
Come here!
- Ah!
- I'll knock you out.
you fuckin' communist cunt!
Hey. hey. hey!
Yeah. same to you!
You fuckin' burned me!
Angela.
What do you got. Andrea?
- Clabby?
- Hearts.
Jump in. the water's warm.
Child's play.
Pound a point.
- Hesh is outside.
- Tell him to come in.
He says he needs
a word with you.
What the fuck? I've eaten
more queens than Lancelot.
What's up?
- Let's walk.
- That serious?
You... spoke
to your uncle lately?
Junior? Yeah.
No. I don't know.
Why? What's up?
Your father
was a fair man. Tony.
What's that got to do
with Junior?
Junior's not so fair.
Hesh. sometimes I wish you'd
just get to the fuckin' point.
- What'd he do?
- He's taxing me. Tony.
He's taxing you?
- When did this happen?
- Today.
Did you tell him you operated
for years without any tax?
That my father loved you
and respected you?
That ten cents out of every
dollar that goes into his kick
is directly related
to your shylock business?
My uncle's been boss of the
family ten fuckin' minutes.
already I got agita.
- What'd you tell him?
- Told him the truth.
It's a reasonable request.
but an unreasonable figure.
Back up a minute.
What do you mean.
"It's a reasonable request?"
He's the boss now. Tony.
He can call the tune.
we all dance to it.
That's the way
it's always been done.
You can either respect
what was done in the past
or change the rules.
Look. Tony. the reason
I came over here
was to tell you.
with all this bullshit
goin' on. I don't know
if I can stay in this area.
- Oh. yeah? Where you gonna go?
- Hey. come on. tatellah.
I can sit
on my royalty checks.
You forget.
I wrote six gold records.
No. a couple of black kids
wrote six gold records.
You owned the company.
You gave yourself
a co-writing credit.
Come on. Heshie.
Besides. I know you.
You leave this action.
you're gonna kill yourself.
How much does he want?
Five hundred large. plus
two points monthly on my shy.
Hm! All right.
Do me a favor.
Sit tight for now.
Let me think about it
for a while.
- ♪ What time is it? ♪
- ♪ It's 7:00 ♪
♪ Just one hour more ♪
- ♪ What time is it? ♪
- ♪ It's 8:00 ♪
♪ Now I'm at her door ♪
♪ What time is it? ♪
♪ It's time ♪
♪ For love ♪
- How was that. baby?
- The best.
You are the best.
Come here.
Tony. I love your cannoli.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Go back to sleep.
Sure you're all right?
So. what do you
want New York to do?
First of all. Junior
can't know that we talked.
He's gotta think that Hesh came
to you on his own by himself.
You are still runnin' things.
Another thing.
the arrangement.
whatever it is. can't be
insulting to my uncle.
Hesh's gotta pay somethin'.
I just haven't decided what.
I gotta get back.
We'll talk later.
- How's the veal?
- It's like rubber.
Yeah?
Tastes all right to me.
- Want somethin' else?
- No.
♪ Happy anniversary to you ♪
Hm. Don't look at me.
Compliments of Johnny Sack.
Maybe you'd like
to spend the rest
of our anniversary with him.
I was over there for ten
friggin' minutes. Carmela.
- Don't do this.
- All right. Tony.
At least I know
where I stand.
Why you always gotta
be so dramatic. huh?
Well. here we go.
All right. I'm sorry. okay?
I'm sorry.
You don't even know what
you're apologizing for.
It's our anniversary. Tony.
Ours. Not yours. mine
and Johnny fuckin' Sacks'.
Ours.
Here I was thinkin' maybe we
could get a room at the Plaza
like last year or.
I don't know.
I don't...
I'm sorry. Carmela. Huh?
I just got a lot on my mind.
and I'm not thinkin' straight.
Hey. I'm sorry.
Should I call the Plaza?
Come on.
Nah. let's go home.
Hey. come here.
Carmela. what do you
want me to say?
Tell me.
I'm lost at sea here.
You've changed. Tony.
and I resent it.
I resent it because
it's destroying what little
self-esteem I have left.
- I swear. sometimes
I think you skeeve me.
- I skeeve you?
What are you talking
about? You're the mother
of my children.
- How the fuck did I skeeve you?
- You see?
You see what I'm talkin' about?
Right there.
"You're the mother
of my children."
I feel like I'm just
someone you've chosen
to procreate with.
You knew this might happen
with the Prozac.
Ginny Torrelli's
been on it for years.
and she'd hump a fire hydrant
if it could make a pass at her.
Hey. Dr. Melfi told me
it affects different
people different ways.
Oh. She told you that?
I think before
we start today's session.
we need to address
the coffee situation.
It's not appropriate of me
to take gifts.
- It's a cup of coffee.
- Let's just make a rule. okay?
No gifts.
- This mean I can't drink mine?
- No. no.
- |
- Oh. I'm sorry.
I usually have my
answering service on
when I have a patient.
but I have a car emergency.
Yes?
What does that mean.
"diagnostic?"
I just wanna know
what's wrong with my car.
No. No. don't do anything.
No. I want to get
a second opinion.
I'll... I'll take my chances.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's all right.
So. how's it goin'?
Good. Real good.
As a matter of fact. I think
I may flush the medication.
You know?
See if the changes I'm feelin'
are for real.
Why would you do that?
The Prozac seems to be working.
Well. that might be
the problem.
It might be workin'
a little overtime.
What do you mean?
- I'm havin' a...
- Reaction?
You know.
a side effect from the stuff.
We talked about that
when you started.
Some people get insomnia. others
a stomach ache or headaches.
But it usually passes.
Are there any other side
effects that you know of?
Some people experience
a diminished libido.
- They have a hard time
getting or maintaining a...
- Bingo.
- I see.
- Mm.
You know. not all impotence
is a result of the medication.
You sayin' there's
somethin' wrong with me?
When's the last time
you had a prostate exam?
Hey. I don't even let anybody
wag their finger in my face.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have laughed!
- Don't apologize.
- Oh. boy.
- You got a nice laugh.
- All right. let's be serious.
Hey. I'm serious.
You know that depression
is also a leading factor
in impotence.
When you awaken
in the morning. or in
the middle of the night.
do you ever have an erection?
You could set
your clock to it.
Okay. so we know it's not
a physical problem.
Let's put that in
after the credenza.
Yes. ma'am.
You wanna tell me
what's goin' on?
I bought some furniture.
Why don't we just move
into Roche Bobois?
Save the delivery charge.
Fine. I'll send it back.
No. but you've been spendi"
like a drunken sailor
all last week.
I said I'll send it back.
Mother of Christ. Carmela.
I didn't say that. did I?
Jesus.
All due respect to New York.
I don't think you should be
tellin' my uncle
ow to run things.
You think I got the balls
to drive in from New York
and tell your uncle how
he should run his family?
I shouldn't expect to see
the Statue of Liberty again
if I did that. huh?
All right. look. Tony.
Hesh isn't only
a friend of you guys.
He's a friend of ours.
Somebody has to step in
so he doesn't get fucked.
I never said fucked.
And you. Frankly.
I'm a little hurt.
You should've come to me first.
Airin' your dirty
laundry in public.
Junior knew how I felt.
How would it look if I went
to you after I spoke to him?
Now. he's got a point.
Bottom line is.
what're we gonna do about this?
Somethin' tells me
you have a suggestion.
Junior. if there are
any flies on you.
they're payin' fuckin' rent.
Five hundred is a little steep
for back taxes. no?
As far as two percent
of his action. that's
up to you to settle.
'Cause. after all. that
affects Tony as much as Hesh.
I'm not out to hurt anyone.
God forbid I get in the way
of someone earning.
Let's say one and a half
on the shy business
and 300 on the back tax.
Two-fifty.
What'd I tell ya?
Hold onto your cock
when you negotiate
with these desert people.
Two-fifty.
All right.
Mr. Soprano.
- You want sex?
- No.
Go back to sleep.
You know.
you have a nice body.
You ought to make it
work for you more.
- Oh. really?
- Yeah. you reveal too much.
You don't want
other men looking at me?
No. When you're not with me.
you do what you want.
But I'm sayin' maybe
you could wear a nice.
businesslike outfit.
I think I could
get into that.
You want me
to dress like a man?
No. No. you fuckin'
whack-a-doo. I don't want
you to dress like a man.
I'm just sayin'.
maybe wear somethin'
a little more professional.
You know.
like you're in business.
Fuck you. Tony.
I'm no whore.
No. That's not what I mean.
Not like you're
in the whore business.
Oh. forget it.
Come here.
Is everybody
in my life bananas or what?
Get over here!
- Come here.
- Go jerk off.
Yeah. Go jerk off.
Look at this.
She burned me.
That's not good.
What led up to that?
Carmela can
be pretty violent sometimes.
This added problem
that I've been havin'
that we talked about...
- Mm-hm.
- I just thought maybe we needed
to spice things up
a little bit. You know?
If it's not the Prozac.
then maybe I just needed
a little jumpstart.
So I suggest to her that maybe
she dress a little different.
Something titillating.
Yeah. You know.
maybe it'd help.
So I suggested to her...
not demanded. suggested...
you know. maybe dress
a little sexier.
But Carmela
can be very sensitive.
Maybe she felt it degraded her.
Not all women are
into sexy lingerie.
I'm not talkin'
about dressin' like that.
Then what are we
talking about?
Some women are sexier
when they dress simple.
You know. understated.
I don't mean...
Fuck it.
I don't know what I mean.
- Like you.
- How like me?
You play it down.
Now. it's obvious you got
a killer body under there.
- Don't get me wrong.
- All right.
Not only do you play it down...
but you're gentle.
Not loud.
Sweet sounding.
Like a mandolin.
Anthony...
It's unfortunate
that we have to stop now.
because I think it's really
important we talk about this.
Do you think you could
come back later this afternoon?
No.
Till Tuesday.
Okay?
Yeah. all right.
See you Tuesday.
Oh. motherfucker!
Ow!
Shit!
It's the oddest thing.
I've had this problem
for weeks.
but this morning I get in
and it starts right up.
- And then again at the deli.
- Looks fine.
Are you sure?
I was told I need a new starter.
Lady. as much
as I might wish to rob you.
even I wouldn't try to replace
a new starter with another.
- What do you mean. "new"?
- New.
It has everything but
the price tag hanging from it.
Come on. Mikey!
I didn't do nothin'!
Yeah. Poor kid committed
suicide up here 'cause of you.
- Come on. You fuckin' know me!
- Yeah. I know ya.
Now. listen to me.
Listen to me. boy.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna give you a break.
When I toss ya over...
- No!
- When I toss you over.
if you can fly.
I won't shoot you down. Deal?
- No!
- Son of a bitch.
Oh!
My goodness.
What happened here?
Some sad shit.
Motherfucker said he
didn't want to live no more.
He jumped.
How much he give you?
I thought I was
the only one Junior
could make look like that.
All right. Let me hear it.
- Rusty Irish.
- What about him?
He took a header off the falls.
That's the closest that junkie
fuck ever got to a bath.
Well. I got news for you.
That junkie fuck was
my biggest earner.
During the football season.
he moved more cards than
ten guys put together.
And another thing.
A certain friend of ours
should've checked with me
before he did a favor
for the old man Capri.
- You're losin' me.
- Irish was the one who sold
Capri's grandson that shit.
I think you created a fucki"
Frankenstein in Junior.
I created? We all agreed
to let Junior have his day.
Let him be the lightning rod.
And when lightning strikes.
God forbid.
and somebody goes down.
it's not a young man with
a family. you remember this?
We all agreed.
Yeah. we agreed.
but who the fuck expected
to get raped over here?
When Jackie was acting boss.
no one minded. 'cause it all
evened out
at the end of the day.
But your uncle. Marone!
Does he eat alone.
He doesn't even pass the salt.
What about that
Sammy Grigio card game?
That fuckin' Mikey
smacked him around.
That ain't right.
Come on. Jimmy. Even a broken
clock is right twice a day.
Junior was right.
He had a position.
That game wasn't payin' anybody.
The minute Sammy Grigio
used Jimmy's name.
it should've been
end of story.
That's right.
What do you want me to do?
Hey. We made our bed.
We sleep in it.
We're all men.
But how long we gonna
continue to kick upstairs
without it hurtin'?
I mean something. anything.
should trickle down
over here. no?
All we want you
to do is talk to him.
After all. he's your uncle.
Come on.
That's right.
- Who is it?
- It's me. Ma.
- Who?
- Anthony.
Open the door.
- I thought you were
the activities lady.
- Hey.
She's a real pain in the ass.
- Playing bingo. Livia?
- Oh. not tonight. honey.
You know. she's
a degenerate gambler.
Millie? Millie?
- Hm?
- My son.
Handsome.
So how's it goin'?
Oh. what can I say?
Hey. this is great.
The only thing that's missin'
is that broken readin' lamp
you had by the phone at home.
And I got it downstairs.
I can bring it if you want.
Shh. shh. Listen.
Oh. she's driving me crazy.
- Who?
- Next door! There it is again.
Oh!
That's enough water!
How much water does she need?
She runs the water all day.
Water. water. water!
I'm livin' next door
to Gunga Din!
I went down to Ferrara's.
I got you some biscotti.
- Almonds?
- Yeah.
All right.
Leave 'em there.
I'll take 'em downstairs
later for my coffee.
- Uncle Jun' been by?
- Oh. once in a while.
He... it makes him
uncomfortable here.
He's got a lot on his mind.
More responsibilities
means more headaches.
Better men than him
had to work hard.
Yeah. He'll be all right.
long as he remembers
who his friends are.
I'd just hate
to see him mess this up.
He's been waitin' a long time
for the big chair.
- What do you mean?
- It's not a business that
forgives bad decisions.
And I hate to see him making
wrong moves. you know?
- Especially at
the start of the game.
- Why're you tellin' me?
- Tell him.
- Ma. you got his ear.
He listens to you.
- I don't know that world.
- No. of course not.
But if anything. you know.
were to come up. that's all.
I don't want to get involved.
If you have something
to say to your uncle.
then bring it up to him.
Oh. I wish
the Lord would take me.
Come on. Ma.
You know. there's
probably plenty of
nice gents in this place
that want a date
with a lovely young
woman like you.
Look. I'm goin' downstairs.
I'm goin' downstairs
before that che bruta
activities lady finds me.
- You want coffee?
- Yeah. all right.
Bring the cookies!
Carmela.
I don't want to sound
like religion is a cure-all.
but I think if Tony would get
more involved with the church.
it may help to expedite
things in his therapy.
What's killing me is that this
is a self-inflicted wound.
I pushed for it.
I could deal
with the goomars.
I knew I was
better than them.
As stupid as it sounds.
I viewed them as a form
of masturbation for him.
I couldn't give him
what he needed all the time.
You're a man. Father.
You know that thirst.
I was too busy with the house
and the kids to quench it.
But the psychiatrist...
You know.
she's not just a goomar.
For the first time. I feel
like he's really cheating.
and I'm the one who's thirsty.
I'm not gonna stay
in a marriage that's made...
Shh. Shh. Let's not
even think about that.
Divorce is for the weak.
for people who never intended
on dying married
in the first place.
You know. Carm.
we reap what we sow.
What do you mean?
You admit to accepting
his dalliances in the past.
They meant nothing to Tony.
But you said it was like they
were lightening the workload.
providing a wife's duty
when you were too busy
with the kids and the house.
You practically welcomed it.
I want you to pray
to our Holy Mother.
Ask her for guidance
and forgiveness
so that you can get
through this as a couple.
You're not without sin
in this. Carmela.
Yeah. so she's outta control.
She's spendin' money like we're
the Sopranos of Park Avenue.
But you've noticed her.
which may have been the point.
Look. before we
run out of time.
I'd like to discuss
what happened when we
were here last week.
How's your car?
Did you steal my car
and have it fixed?
No gifts.
I didn't want
to see you get robbed.
It was you.
You had no right
to steal my car.
- I've been scared to death.
- Why?
Why? It's a violation
of my privacy.
What else have you done?
Answer me.
I love you.
- Anthony...
- I'm in love with you.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way it is.
- Okay. let me talk.
- No. It's not the Prozac.
I dream about you.
I think about you
all the time.
I can't get excited
about any other women.
There's nothing else to say.
- I love you.
- Let me start here.
I know this may be very hard
for you to swallow...
but you're only feeling
this way because we've
made such progress.
- What?
- I've been gentle.
That's my job.
I listen.
That's what I do best.
I've been a broad. generic.
sympathetic woman to you.
because that's what
this work calls for.
You've made me all
of the things you feel
are missing in your wife
and in your mother.
You're makin' me out
to be some fuckin' mama's boy.
I'm a man.
and you're a woman.
End of story.
And this crap about Freud.
and every boy wanting
to have sex with his mother.
that's not gonna fly here.
I didn't say that.
I want to make sure we
understand each other.
Yeah. we understand
each other.
You don't love me.
You don't want me
to come back any more. fine.
It's quite the opposite.
This is all a byproduct
of progress.
Has someone been following me?
Okay. forget it.
I'll see you next week.
All right! Let's go!
Move it!
Uncle Junior. remember
when you used to tell me...
I always thought
you could make the pros.
You coulda done it.
You had a swing like Joe D.
- You're crazy.
- What. you think
I'm shittin' you?
Yeah. I could barely hit .250.
That's because
you didn't want it.
Too busy chasin' skirt.
Chasin' skirt.
your average was .500.
Yeah. what happened?
So what is it
you wanted to talk about?
Octavian.
You know. Augustus.
- You fuckin' with me?
- No.
Octavian became Augustus.
Forget about that.
Bottom line.
Augustus was a Caesar.
And everybody
loved him. right?
You know why?
I don't know
that I give a fuck.
Everybody loved him
'cause he never ate alone.
Capisce?
It was the longest time
of peace in Rome's history.
He was a fair leader.
and all his people
loved him for that.
This the one that they
stabbed in the back?
No. that was Julius.
I'm talkin' about Augustus.
He shared his wealth.
and all his people loved him.
You said that three
fuckin' times. I heard it.
"His people loved him."
What's your fuckin' point?
You remember the story you
told me about the father bull
talkin' to the son?
They're up on this hill.
They're lookin' down
on a bunch of cows.
"Dad. why don't we
run down there
and fuck one of these cows?"
And you remember
what the father said?
Father says. "Son.
why don't we walk down there
and fuck 'em all?"
- I told you that?
- Yeah!
Why don't we fuck 'em all!
That's funny.
Okay. I get your point.
Why didn't you just
come out with it.
instead of all this
fuckin' Augustus-
Octavian shit?
I don't know.
Are you okay?
You been actin'
mezzo morte lately.
I ain't seen
a long face like that
since you were a kid.
I'm okay. It's just...
bullshit stuff.
Don't worry about it.
- You sure?
- Yeah. yeah. I'm okay.
Junior took the 250
you gave him and whacked it up
amongst the top five guys.
- You know.
so he doesn't look greedy.
- Smart move.
- Yeah.
- Your uncle may turn out
to be another Harry Truman.
- What's that mean?
- Truman had a big job
thrust upon him.
He didn't want it.
but in the end he made
some pretty wise decisions.
So who knows?
Your uncle may turn out to be
the right man for the job.
I fuckin' hope so.
'cause I'll tell you right now.
I don't want the fuckin' job.
Let Junior die from the stress.
It's what gave Jackie
the cancer. God rest his soul.
Boss. Fuck it.
Who needs it?
It's nice here.
I can't stand the smell.
Shit. flies
all over the place.
But I could stand here
for hours and watch
'em run around.
There's a kind of
beauty to it.
- I envy them.
- I wouldn't go that far.
I would.
They got no bills.
no headaches.
no family cazzis
runnin' around.
One horse likes another horse.
they go up to each other.
they fuck. That's it.
No problems.
no hundred questions.
no guilt.
I don't know what the fuck
I'm talkin' about.
So Junior whacked up my money.
and he's gonna spread it
around. huh?
Yeah.
Five bosses. 50 a pop?
Not a bad day's pay.
Still. I wish it
wasn't your money.
You know.
it makes me feel terrible.
What?
You old fuckin' Jew.
Here's my share.
Think I'm gonna
profit off of your tax?
Never entered my mind.
Dr. Melfi. There's
nothin' there. you know.
You don't have
to explain nothin'. Tony.
This psychiatry shit.
apparently. what you're feelin'
is not what you're feelin'.
and what you're not feelin'
is your real agenda.
You're gonna stick
with it. right?
- I don't know.
- I think you should.
- You do?
- Uh-huh.
I was jealous.
- I should've told you...
- No. wait. Let me finish. Tony.
I've been thinki"
a lot about this.
I was jealous of her
ability to help you...
to be a sort
of salvation to you.
I talked to Father Phil. and...
I wanna be that
woman in your life.
Carm. you aren't
just in my life.
You are my life.
Come here.
Okay. I'm no good at speeches.
Yeah. you owe him
a fuckin' dime. you'll
hear some great speeches.
Shut up. Your Honor.
Let me talk.
Go ahead. talk.
I was only kiddin'. Go ahead.
All right. I'd like everybody
to raise their glasses.
Okay...
He taught me as much as anybody.
except for maybe my father.
Even if he wasn't my uncle.
I'd be standin' here sayin'.
to our new boss. salute.
To Junior.
Junior.
- To Junior.
- Salute.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-